

GIGA ADRIEL

Location: DKI Jakarta, Indonesia Mobile: 0838 9562 2962

Email: giga.adriel@gmail.com

PERSONAL

Graduated from Faculty of Law, Universitas Indonesia in 2019 and has been working in law firms ever since. Experienced in dealing with various legal corporate works and used with a fast-paced working environment that requires delivery of works in an effective and efficient ways and ability to work individually and in a team.

EDUCATION

Universitas Indonesia (2015 – 2019)

Sarjana Hukum (Bachelor of Law), 3.29 out of 4.00 GPA

SMA Negeri 14, Jakarta (2013 - 2015)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Widyawan & Partners in association with Linklaters (March 2021 - present)

Junior Associate at Widyawan & Partners in association with Linklaters (September 2021 - present)
Legal Intern at Widyawan & Partners in association with Linklaters (March 2021 – September 2021)

- Preparing corporate secretarial documents (Shareholders' Resolution, Shareholders' Register, Collective Shares' Certificates, BOD Resolutions);
- Liaising with notaries and governmental institutions;
- Reviewing agreements;
- Preparing legal memos and legal opinions;
- Preparing Offering Memorandums for global bonds issuance of prominent multi-national companies;
- Conducting legal due diligence of prominent companies.

Jusuf Indradewa & Partners Legal Consultants (November 2019 – March 2021)

Junior Associate

- Conducting legal due diligence of prominent companies in Indonesia regarding the issuance of corporate bonds, such as PT Sampoerna Agro Tbk, PT Pelabuhan Indonesia I (Persero), and PT Global Mediacom Tbk;
- Preparing syndicated-loan agreements;
- Preparing legal memos and legal opinions.

Waruwu & Partners Law Firm (June – September 2018)

Legal Intern

Conducting legal due diligence of a prominent bank in Indonesia.

Toyota Astra Financial Services (*December 2017 – January 2018*)

Intern

- Reviewing customer financing contracts;
- Administering legal documents.

ORGANISATIONAL / VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Chairman of the Youth Commission of GKP Ebenhaezer Cawang (2014-2019)

• Arranging annual programs of the commission;

- Supervising the execution of the annual programs;
- Accomodating and foster skills among the youth;
- Preparing monthly and yearly financial reports and program reports

AWARD AND RECOGNITION

- 1st rank: Highest score on the School Exam in SMAN 14 Jakarta
- 2nd rank: Highest score on the National Exam in SMAN 14 Jakarta
- 1st winner: Band Competition in SMAN 79 Jakarta
- 2nd winner: Band Competition in SMAN 8 Jakarta